-好的  钱德勒  -好
- Okay, Chandler. - Okay.
你的星座运势说
And your horoscope says:
本月五日  某个特别的人会送你礼物
"On the 5th, a special someone will give you a gift. "
那就先谢了
Well, thank you in advance.
却会在十二日引发口角
"But the 12th brings a lover's spat. "
你要取笑我送你的礼物
You are going to make a joke about my special present!
你干嘛这么嘴贱
Why would you do that?
十九日  会有秘密爱慕者向你表白
Wait. "On the 1 9th, a secret crush announces itself. "
大家好
Hey, guys.
天啊  是"麦克与起司"的乔伊·崔比安尼
lt's Joey Tribbiani of Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
也对  你今天开拍
That's right. lt's your first day.
和机器人拍档打击假犯罪  激不激动啊
So are you psyched to fight fake crime with your robot sidekick?
还用问吗  在连续剧里担当主角
Am I psyched? The lead in my own TV series?
这是我多年来的梦想
l've dreamed about this for years!
怎么可能没有准备好
Why have l not been preparing?
乔伊  你一定会演得很棒
No! Joey, you’re going to be great!
但我得跟机器人对戏  菲比
But l gotta act with a robot. Phoebe.
我对科技一窍不通
l know nothing about technology.
钱德勒的电脑  我只会用来找黄片
l can't even use Chandler's computer, except to find porn.
那还是因为一打开  就在那里了
And-and that’s only'cause it's right there when you turn it on!
看来我们本月份的口角会提前发生
I think our lover’s spat will start a little early this month.
我等你
l'll be waiting.
你是在看封面来评价内容吗
Are you judging them by their covers?
因为这样不对喔
Cause you're really not supposed to do that.
不是  我想选一本来用
l'm deciding which one to use.
我又要写书了
I’m gonna start writing another book.
因为上一本很畅销吗
Because the last one was such a big seller?
告诉你  我已经写了十四本书了
lf you must know, l have written 14 books.
因为读者只有我一个
And as l'm the only one who has read them...
我可以告诉你们  每本书口碑都很好
I can tell you that they all have been very well received.
你们等一下有事吗
What are you doing later?
瑞秋和我要去剪头发
Oh, Rachel and I have appointments to get our hair-cut.
-有吗    -我想先知道他要干嘛
- We do? - l wanna see what he wants.
我刚得知伊丽莎白她爸想见我
Elizabeth's dad wants to meet me.
等等  且慢
Wait a minute. Hold the phone.
你不是伊丽莎白的爸爸吗
You're not Elizabeth's dad?
拜托啦  我真的想让他喜欢我
Look, come on guys, I-I really want this guy to like me.
你们要是能帮着
It-it would really help me out
捧我一下就太好了
if you guys were here to kinda make me look good.
-我们当然会帮忙了  -谢谢
- Of course we'll help. - Thanks.
谁都知道参加家长会很辛苦
We know how tough those parent- teacher conferences can be.
这是你的办公室场景
So here's your office set.
麦克·麦可维利  私家侦探
Mac Machiavelli, private investigator.
好啦  我带你去试戏服
OK. Let’s get you into wardrobe for a fitting.
什么时候跟机器人见面
OK. When do l meet the robot?
抱歉  那就现在吧  他也在
I’m sorry, why don’t we do that right now? He’s right here.
乔伊·崔比安尼  这位...
Joey Tribbiani, this is...
真是栩栩如生啊
Wow! He's so lifelike.
了不起
Unbelievable.
这位是创造  操作起司的韦恩
This is Wayne, the man who created and operates C.H.E.E.S.E.
韦恩  你好
How do you do there, buddy?
-你们两个了解下对方  -好的
- l'll let you two guys get acquainted. - Okay.
刚才很抱歉
Sorry about that.
-起司在那里呢   -起司就在这里
- So where's C.H.E.E.S.E.? - C.H.E.E.S.E. is right here.
麦克  幸会
Nice to meet you, Mac.
-它是半成品吧   -不是  怎么了
- This is the temporary robot, right? - No. Why?
我以为它会长得很酷呢
l thought it was gonna be a really cool robot.
像魔鬼终结者  或第一眼看到你一样真
Like the Terminator, or when l first saw you.
我花了两年研发这台机器
l spent two years developing this machine.
它非常先进
it’s absolutely state of the art.
抱歉  只是它看起来一无是处
Sorry. lt doesn't look like it can do anything.
它会这样
lt can do this.
这是我爸  保罗·史提芬斯
This is my father, Paul Stevens.
爸  这是罗斯·盖勒
Dad, this is Ross Geller.
保罗  你好
lt's great to meet you, Paul.
我喜欢伊丽莎白的男友  叫我史提芬斯先生
Usually l prefer that Liz's boyfriends address me as Mr. Stevens.
没问题  史提芬斯先生
Of course. Mr. Stevens.
罗斯...
So, Ross...
你有什么毛病
...what's your problem?
什么
Excuse me?
为什么交不到年龄相近的女友
Why can't you get a girlfriend your own age?
真好笑...
lt's funny....
不好笑
lt's not funny.
我不喜欢你跟我女儿交往  罗斯
l don't like you going out with my daughter, Ross.
好  我看得出来
Okay, l can see that.
你给我个机会  我一定能改变你的看法
But l think if you give me one chance, l can change your mind.
-好  -什么
- Okay. - What?
好  我给你个机会来改变我的看法
Okay. l'll give you one chance to change my mind.
给你一分钟
You've got one minute.
-爸  -好吧  两分钟  开始
- Daddy. - Fine. Two minutes. Go.
一分五十秒
A minute and 50 seconds.
好  我以前没做过这种事
l want you to know, l've never done anything like this before.
我是说我跟别人交往过
l mean, l've been in relationships in general.
但是我没跟学生做过...不...
But l've never done it with a student. l mean, not....
不是那档事  我们还没做过
Not "it." "We haven't done "it. "
当然我们做过一些事...
l mean, we've done stuff....
好  讲个笑话轻松一下
Okay. Okay. A joke. A joke. Lighten the mood.
两个男人走进酒吧  一个是爱尔兰人
Two guys go into a bar. One of them is lrish.
-我是爱尔兰人  -结果爱尔兰人赢了
- l'm lrish. - And the lrish guy wins the joke.
罗斯  居然会在这里遇见你
Ross! How crazy that we would run into you.
天啊  谢谢你们
Oh, my God! Thank you.
史提芬斯先生  他们是我朋友
Mr. Stevens. l'd like you to meet my friends.
菲比  摩妮卡和钱德
This is Phoebe, Monica and Chandler.
你是伊丽莎白的父亲
You're Elizabeth's father, huh?
难怪她有一种
I can see now where she gets her
粗犷的美
rugged handsomeness.
你有老婆吗
ls there a Mrs. Stevens?
你有老公
There's a Mr. Bing!
没有  丽莎刚出生不久  她妈妈就过世了
No, unfortunately Lizzie’s mom passed away shortly after she was born.
是我一手把她带大
l raised her by myself.
我常碰上这种反应
l get that a lot.
好  大家都坐吧
OK. Why don't we all take a seat? You know,
我去帮大家点个咖啡
and I’ll get us all some some coffees.
你来
Yeah, why don't you....
你们先随便聊  随便聊哈
you guys can talk about whatever, whatever you want.
想到什么  就聊什么
Whatever pops into your head.
这时候在这里遇见罗斯真怪
lt is strange seeing Ross here, this time of day...
通常这时候他都是在儿童医院呢
...because usually he's at the children's hospital.
不是去泡小妞儿喔
But not looking for dates.
莫妮卡是罗斯的妹妹
So Monica is Ross's sister.
他是个很棒的哥哥
He's a great brother!
我也有一个妹妹
l had a sister.
她过世了
She passed away.
你们不必每次都这种反应
You don't have to do that every time.
不过罗斯人真的很好  我们是大学室友
But Ross is a great guy. l was roommates with him in college.
好笑的是...
Funny story....
你的大学室友死了  对吧
Your roommate in college died, didn't he?
他算是半死不活吧
A part of him did, yes.
来吧  保罗  伊丽莎白
OK. Here we are, Paul, Elizabeth.
希望你们有找到话题
l hope you guys are finding something to talk about.
-我们正在...  -抱歉我来晚了
- Yes. We were just... - Sorry l'm late.
不过我已经准备好要捧你了
But l am ready, ready to talk you up.
-伊丽莎白的爸爸什么时候来  -我已经来了
- When does Liz's father get here? - l'm already here.
罗斯人最好了
Ross is so great!
你买印有小女生的那种
Honey, you got the kind with the little girl.
你明明说要买印有小宝宝的那种手纸啊
You said you'd buy the kind with the baby.
你说那个小宝宝有点恐怖
You said the baby creeps you out.
是小女生恐怖
No, the little girl creeps me out.
-你是说小宝宝  -小宝宝为什么会恐怖
- You said the baby. - Why would a baby creep me out?
那小女生为什么会恐怖
Why would the little girl creep you out?
抱歉  你们讲慢一点好吗
You guys, I’m sorry, Can you please talk a little slower?
你要写进书里啊
This is for your book?
对  这是探讨男女关系的书
Yeah. lt's about relationships.
尔虞我诈  各种禁忌
You know, the traps, the pitfalls, what not to do.
继续  太精彩了
Keep going. This stuff's great.
你说什么
Excuse me.
还有真心相爱就能克服一切
And how none of it matters when the people really love each other.
还有所有人都喜欢
And how people will believe anything you tell them
听好话
as long as it's a compliment.
-你好  -你好
- Oh hi! - Hi!
我把钥匙掉在这里了
l left my keys here somewhere.
那赶快找吧
Well, let's look for them.
是这一串吗
Hey, look! Are these them?
不是
No.
好吧
All right.
-在这里  -太好了
- Here they are. - Good.
-谢谢你  -抱歉  稍等一下
- Thanks for your help. - Wait! Sorry!
-保罗先生  -叫我保罗就好
- Mr. Paul? - Just call me Paul.
保罗  我只是想说
Paul. l just wanted you to know that...
罗斯人真的很好
you know, Ross really is a great guy.
不如你跟他交往吧
Well maybe you could date him.
省得我宰掉他的功夫
lt'd save me the trouble of killing him.
怎么了
Are you okay?
你不像是有二十岁女儿的人
You don't look old enough to have a 20-year-old daughter.
我们生她的时候很年轻
Well, we were very young when we had her.
-什么我们  -一男一女才能...
- We? - lt usually takes two people to....
当然  我知道
Oh, no! Yes! Of course. l know that!
心中还是两个人吗  还是只剩下你了
What l meant was are you still "we" or are you just you?
只有我
l'm just me.
丽莎出生没多久  我老婆就死了
My wife died shortly after Lizzie was born.
你一手把她带大吗
So you raised her all on your own?
对
Yes, l did.
第一天顺利吗
How was your first day?
不错  但机器人的态度有点差
Pretty good. Except l got attitude from the robot.
那些死机器人  它们应该是人类忠实的仆人
Damn those robots. They're supposed to be our faithful servants!
总之不是机器人  是操作它的人
Anyway, it was the guy who controls the robot.
他不喜欢我
Yeah, he doesn’t like me.
我正要拿三明治  他就让起司
He had C.H.E.E.S.E. knock over the sandwich table...
打翻装三明治的桌子
...right when l was reaching for one.
你怎么不让他滚呢
Why don't you get him fired?
搞不好我会  我也不想  但我是主角
l may have to. l hate to do it. But l'm the star, you know?
总不能老捡地上的三明治吃
There's a limit to how many sandwiches l can eat off the floor.
抱歉
Excuse me.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
小子  找到你就好  有试镜
Joe! l'm glad l found you! l got an audition for you.
这件事是个秘密
But it's kind of on the q. t.
那个演员不知道  他可能会被换掉
The actor who has the part doesn't know he might be fired.
是一部影集的主角
lt's the lead in a series.
"麦克与起司"
Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
我就是"麦克与起司"的主角
l'm the lead in Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
乔伊
Joey?
你好啊  罗斯
Hi, Ross.
我在让他喜欢你
l was just getting him to like you.
乔伊
Joey!
罗斯  乔伊不在
Ross, Joey is not here.
好  那我在房里面等
OK. l'll just wait for him in here!
罗斯  没关系  你可以出来
Ross, it's okay. You can come out.
对啊  罗斯  没关系  是我
Yeah, Ross. lt's okay. lt's me...
史提芬斯先生
...Mr. Stevens.
天啊  我刚才没看见你
l didn't.... Oh, my gosh. l didn't even see you.
当然有  你走进来
You did. You came in,
觉得很窘  就跑进房里去
got all awkward and ran to the bedroom.
还大叫"乔伊  乔伊"
You were shouting, "Joey! Joey!"
-再见  瑞秋  -再见
- Bye, Rachel. - Bye.
我再打给你
l'll call you later.
-好  再见  -罗斯  再见
- Okay, See you. - Bye, Ross.
你  你怎么  你在怎么
What? What the...? How did...? What?
他的钥匙掉了  就回来找啊
Well, you know, he lost his keys. So he was looking for them.
在你的嘴里找吗
ln your mouth?
不是
No!
在楼下找  我们就聊了起来
Downstairs. And we got to talking...
聊了有两小时吧
you know, for two hours.
我很喜欢他
and I really liked him
就请他上来喝杯咖啡
so I invited him up here for a cup of coffee.
你们就在咖啡馆里
You were at the coffeehouse!
罗斯  就算我亲了他又怎样
Ross, What's the big deal? So l kissed the guy.
他是我的女朋友的爸爸  这样很怪
He is my girlfriend's father. OK? lt's weird!
-你还不是跟我妹约会  -那不一样
- What? You dated my sister! - That was different!
-为什么  -这次是我觉得怪
- What? Why? - This is weird for me!
罗斯  这样对你有好处
Ross, look, look. This is good for you. OK?
承认吧  目前他一点也不喜欢你
Let's face it. So far the guy's not loving you.
但我可以扭转形势  我有门路了
But l can turn that around. l've got the inside track.
我们可以一起去吃饭  我可以把你捧上天
We could all go out to dinner, y’know? And I can talk you up!
况且他是个非常非常成功的律师
Plus the guy is a very very successful lawyer.
-这个为什么重要  -可重要了
- How is that important? - lt's important!
结果有一大票人可以演麦克
Apparently, There's a million guys who can play Mac...
但机器人
...and there's one robot.
和操作员却都只有一个
And this one guy who controls it.
我不知道他让我失业了
l didn't know he could get me fired.
我该怎么办
What am l gonna do?
乔伊  你很有魅力
Well, you know, Joey, you're a pretty charming guy.
谢了  但我有问题要解决
Thanks. But l have a problem to deal with.
不  亲爱的  你得让那个操作员喜欢你
No, sweetie, you've got to win over the guy who controls C.H.E.E.S.E.
你得用力拍他的机器马屁
Go back there and kiss some serious robot ass!
这个主意不错
That's not a bad idea!
既然明天要施展魅力
lf l have to be charming tomorrow,
现在还是别浪费在你们身上好
l'm not wasting it on you guys.
不过菲比  我为你留了一点
Well, actually I got a little bit saved for you Pheebs.
你觉得乔伊比我有魅力吗
Do you think Joey is more charming than me?
对  所以我跟他有一腿
Yeah. That's why l'm sleeping with him on the side.
你想得美喔
You wish.
"你想得美喔"
"You wish. "
菲比  别再写我们了
Stop writing about us.
我没有写你  我是在写别人
l'm not writing about you. l'm writing about other people.
-谁  -莫莎和钱特
- Who? - Marsha and Chester.
好  很好
Okay fine! Fine!
那我就来写菲莉丝
Then you know what? l will just write about Phyllis.
菲莉丝坐在椅子上
"Phyllis is sitting in the chair. "
我知道你想干嘛
l see what you're doing.
菲莉丝知道我想干嘛
"Phyllis sees what l'm doing. "
哎哟  我终于自食恶果了  苦死了
l have tasted my own medicine and it is bitter!
早
Morning!
我最欣赏的天才  和我的机器人兄弟好吗
How's my favorite genius and his robot?
-别碰他  -好
- Don't touch him! - Okay.
韦恩  你老实说
All right. Umm, all right Wayne, Level with me.
我一直听说我会被换掉
Okay? l keep hearing rumors that l might get fired.
他们还找人来试我这个角色
Okay, they even have actors coming in to read for my part!
拜托啦  再给我一次机会
Come on, man. You gotta give me a second chance.
我爱死这个小家伙...
l love this little guy.
好吧  难怪你不让我碰他  拿去吧
OK. That's why you didn't want me to touch him, right? Here you go.
我真是白痴  真是的
l can't believe it. God!
你好吗
Hey, how are you doing?
我的高中毕业舞会舞伴似乎放我鸽子
So it seemed that my prom date had stood me up.
罗斯义不容辞地站了出来
So Ross selflessly offered to take me.
好感人喔
What a nice story.
罗斯上大学时
So Ross was in college...
想趁虚而入
...and decided to jump at the chance
带一名少女参加高中舞会
to take a young girl to her high school prom.
想不到会有这种反效果
l definitely did not see that one backfiring.
-我去洗手间  -你慢慢上
- l'm going to the bathroom. - Take your time.
其实我是大一  她是高三
l was a freshman and she was a senior.
所以没有差很多...
So it wasn't as bad as...
罗斯  我知道我一直找你麻烦
Look. l know l've been giving you a lot of jabs.
是因为我爱女心切
lt's partly because l'm very protective of Lizzie...
而且你的丑事一件接一件
...and partly because they just keep coming to me.
我必须承认  丽莎一直夸你
l admit after all the wonderful things Lizzie told me...
瑞秋又说了那么那么那么多事
...and the many, many, many stories that Rachel has told me...
看来
...well...
你也...没
...you're not...
那么糟
...all bad.
是没那么糟
"Not all bad. "
很抱歉之前对你那么凶  你必须知道
l'm sorry l was so harsh before. But you have to understand.
丽莎在我眼中仍是个12岁小女孩
l still look at Lizzie like she's a 12-year-old girl.
我懂你的意思  我也有深有同感
Yeah. You know what, I know what you mean. l do that too.
你说什么
l beg your pardon?
不不不  我不是把她当成12岁的小女孩
No! No! Not—I don’t mean I-I see her as a twelve-year-old girl!
我是说我有个六岁的儿子
l mean, l have a son who is 6
在我眼中  他仍是个小宝宝
and l still think of him as a baby.
-你有儿子啊  -对  我和前妻有共同监护权
- A son? - My ex-wife and l share custody of Ben.
还有  卡萝尔和我的关系很好
Just to let you know, Carol and l are on excellent terms...
相信你和你太太也是
...as l'm sure you are with your wife.
抱歉
l'm sorry.
我真是猪
lt's unbelievable!
没事  我只是不知道你结过婚
Don't worry. l didn't realize you were married.
我们是结过婚  那只是...
We were. But that was just a....
那只是酒后的大错误
I mean that was just a big drunken mistake.
你回来了
You're back.
你们结过婚吗
You two were married?
抱歉  你在讲艾米丽啊
l'm sorry. You were talking about Emily.
钱德勒  我们是约六点在楼下咖啡店见
Chandler, we said we would meet at the coffeehouse at 6:00.
我们是约七点
We said 7:00.
我们是约六点
We said 6:00!
我如果有讲到六点这个字
The only way that l said 6:00...
应该是说
...would be if l said the sentence,
我们约七点  不要约六点
"Let's meet at 7:00, not at 6:00."
我如果有讲到七点  应该是说
lf l had said 7:00, maybe I would’ve said something like this,
"我男朋友真自作聪明  七点"
"My boyfriend is such a wiseass. 7:00!"
-你们好啊  -我的天啊
- Hi! - Oh, my good God!
-我知道你们约几点  -什么
- l know what time you said. - What?
老实说  我知道莫莎和钱特约几点
Well actually, I know what time Chester and Marcia said.
几点
What time?
真有趣的转变啊
lnteresting turn of events.
我的书突然成了救星  我看看哈
Suddenly it's my book to the rescue. Let's see.
有意思
Very interesting.
这样就很清楚了
Well this certainly clears things up.
到底是几点
What does it say?
你们先感谢我写这本书  我就告诉你
l will tell you as soon as you thank me for writing my book.
谢谢你写书  这真是一本好书
Thank you for writing your book. lt's a great book...
你是万物之女王
...and you are the queen of everything.
谢谢  你也是
Thanks. So are you.
我就说我不该穿这个颜色
l told you l should not wear this color.
莫...莫莎和钱特
"Monica... Marsha and Chester
打算星期天晚上去看电影
are planning on seeing a movie Sunday night.
摩莎觉得应该约六点
"Marsha thinks they're meeting at 6:00.
钱特觉得电影是七点
Chester thinks it's 7:00."
-你知道我们会赶不上电影  -没错
- So you knew we were gonna miss the movie? - That's right.
你不告诉我们
lnstead of telling us,
却只把它写进你的蠢书里吗
you decided to write it in your stupid book?
莫莎和钱特很气菲莉丝
"Marsha and Chester are mad at Phyllis. "
我居然要被换角
l can't believe l'm gonna lose this job.
真可惜  我能帮什么忙吗
l'm so sorry, man. ls there anything l can do?
能  别让保安看见  帮我偷搬小冰箱
Yeah. Help me get this mini- fridge past the security guard.
乔伊  我有事找你
Joey, l want to talk to you.
我可不想理你  韦恩
l don't want to talk to you Wayne.
我恨你  你毁了我的一生
l hate you. You ruined my life.
钱德勒  韦恩  韦恩  钱德
Chandler, Wayne. Wayne, Chandler. Hi.
乔伊  如果你帮我  我就叫他们不要换角
Joey. Joey. l'll get you your job back if you help me out.
我为什么要帮你
Why should l help you out?
-理由他已经说了  -有何能效劳
- The reason he just said. - What do you need?
我看到你跟那个美女说话
l saw you on stage talking to that beautiful woman.
就是莎拉  我很想跟她说话
You know, Sarah. l wish l could talk to her.
-你爱上她了吗   -对
- Are you in love with her or something? - Yeah.
她  所有的女人  谁都好
Her. All of them. Anyone.
我也是过来人  朋友
Yeah. l've been there, my friend.
你教我跟女人搭讪
Listen, l guarantee you keep your job...
我保证让你留下来
...if you can teach me to talk to women like you do.
韦恩  这种事是教不来的
Wayne, it's not really something you can teach y'know?
这是一种天生的...
It's pretty much something you're born with if you
不不  这当然可以教  我马上教你
You-you can teach it! I’ll show you right how to do it.
其实我在想
I mean, if you think about it...
罗斯每次结婚  都学到一点东西
...Ross did learn something from each marriage.
学到如何让婚姻变得更短吗
How to make the next one even shorter?
等等  这么说不公平
Wait a minute. That's not fair.
他和我的婚姻  比跟艾米丽的婚姻长多了
He was married to me a hell of a lot longer than he was to Emily.
只是他没告诉我
He just didn't tell me.
我再撒一次尿好了
Maybe l have to pee again.
真有意思
Well, this is fun.
罗斯  有哪个老婆被你杀了吗
So, Ross, did you kill any of these wives?
你知道吗   我受够了
l have had enough of this!
我很喜欢你的女儿
You know, l care a great deal about your daughter.
我一直很尊重她
and I have treated her with nothing but respect!
要是你对我有意见  说实话...
So if you've got a problem with me...frankly…
-你在吼我吗  -绝对没有
- Are you yelling at me? - God, no.
爸  如果你不喜欢罗斯  也无所谓
You know what? Daddy. lf you don't like Ross, that's fine.
我不管  我还是要跟他交往
lt doesn't matter to me. l'm going out with him anyway.
真的吗
Really?
要是她不管
Well, if it doesn't matter to her...
那我也不管  这也不是吼你喔
...it doesn't matter to me. Still not yelling.
那就没办法了
What can l say?
但我还是不欣赏你
This doesn't make me like you any better!
没关系  我也不太喜欢我自己
That’s okay, I’m not so crazy about myself right now either.
-我们达成共识了吗  -对吧
- Then we agree? - Yeah. l guess so.
-我们没有人喜欢罗斯  -我喜欢罗斯
- Neither of us like Ross. - l like Ross.
小孩子
Kids!
等等  我又想到罗斯人很好的实例了
Wait, wait. l just thought of a story about how nice Ross is.
没关系  瑞秋  我们现在不喜欢罗斯
That's okay. Rach. We're not liking Ross right now.
这种实例也很多
Well, l got a lot of those too.
事实证明你是对的  起司
Well, it turns out you were right, C.H.E.E.S.E.
-那批货根本没抵达阿马哈  -没错
- The shipment never made it to Omaha? - You got it.
而且那个拉比的胡子  根本是马毛
And the rabbi's beard? 100 percent horsehair.
干得好  起司
Nice catch, C.H.E.E.S.E.
起司  该你了
lt's your line, C.H.E.E.S.E.
韦恩  韦恩
Wayne! Wayne!